Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
(MAN EXHALES)
KEVIN: (AS DENNIS) We keep bringing him
sacred food and nothing's happening.
The Beast. he's shown himself.
twice.
to the masses
of the broken and...
And they're not believing.
There's no revolution.
(AS PATRICIA) Dennis.
Do not be scared.
You have to trust me.
As you always have.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(AS PATRICIA)
Look at you all.
My name is Patricia.
Now. who'd like
a PB and J sandwich?
You do.
(MAN GROANS)
T: (EXCLAIMS) Boom!
Whoo!
Ooh!
Ah! Look at him!
Oh.
The master. boy.
Superman punch. bitch! Yeah!
(LAUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
Whoo!
MAN: Hey!
RONALD:
Go. go. go! Get out!
MAN: You all right. brother?
(MAN GROANING ON VIDEO)
T: (EXCLAIMS) Boom!
Ooh. You see his bag fall?
It's what they call
"dramatic effect."
This is gonna get
so many views.
(DOOR RATTLING)
Is that a raccoon again?
(DOOR OPENS)
Did you leave the door open. T?
I closed it.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Hello?
(WATER RUNNING)
Yo. who's there?
We about to Salt Bae your ass.
(FAUCET TURNS OFF)
(SWITCH CLICKS)
T: Superman punch him. Ronald.
(LOUD THUDDING)
(ROLAND GRUNTING)
(PUNCHES LANDING)
T: Oh. shit. It's you!
(WHIMPERING)
(KEYS JANGLING)
(SHUTTER CREAKING)
(DOOR LOCKING)
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
(MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
DAVID: They bumped into me
at the subway.
Can't just
let them go. Joseph.
Weren't you on
a specified walk?
You can't run this like the store.
It's potluck.
All things come second when
we're on a specified walk.
Store works
because we have rules.
Hey. it was
a good follow. though.
"We gonna Salt Bae your ass."
What a douche.
It's definitely
going into the book.
"Salt Bae your ass."
DAVID:
But what is that. anyway?
It's an Internet guy. He's a butcher
who salts his meat in an elaborate way.
You got dinged.
And good news.
They're not calling you "The
Tip-Toe Man" or "The Float" anymore.
They're pretty much settled
on "The Overseer."
It's cool.
Do not mention
"The Tip-Toe Man" ever again.
That's all he does?
He seasons meat?
Dad. you look tired.
Why don't we save the next walk
for the day after tomorrow?
DAVID: When we find this Horde.
I'll take a mental health day.
Okay. Fine.
I have a new tenuous theory.
Let's call it "Tenuous
Theory Number Two."
The first set of girls
that were found mutilated
at the zoo three weeks ago
happened here.
The second set here.
Now. these new girls that went missing
create kind of a messy triangle.
And where you were waiting
today at the subway
was in the middle
of this triangle.
In Tenuous Theory Number Two.
he isn't in this triangle.
He's coming from a place that has easy
access to this triangular feeding zone.
I think he's somewhere here.
Dad. In the factory area.
DAVID: Okay.
I'll walk
around there tomorrow.
Hey. Dad.
I'm checking
the police scanners.
They're looking for you
pretty aggressively.
Be real careful.
All right.
REPORTER: (ON RADIO) Philadelphia
has a new tallest building.
The Osaka Tower is taking over
the city skyline.
The architecture makes
it an amazing sight to see.
And on top of that.
it's the ultimate in sustainability.
It gets its power from solar panels.
Developers say it will...
(CHAIR SCRAPES)
(PAN SIZZLING)
(UTENSIL CLINKING)
Audrey. I have
to tell you something.
Audrey.
(FOOTSTEPS TAPPING)
(AS HEDWIG) Miss Patricia
said that I'm not allowed
to play with you guys. so don't even ask.
(SNIFFLES)
I had a girlfriend once.
You don't know her.
We kissed.
It's no big deal.
Stop messing with us.
What do you want?
Vera! Don't get him angry.
He's sick.
Don't tell me names.
They said not to ask
you your names
because I might get sad.
you know?
After tonight.
Why did you
pick us. Hedwig?
Oh. because you're impure and
you haven't done any suffering.
(VOCALIZING)
You know that boy band stuff?
Some of it's okay.
but Drake?
Drake's my new main man.
The Beast is gonna come for
you guys any minute now.
And I get to greet him.
It's my big reward for keeping
the Horde in the light.
I get to take him
to the masses of the broken.
I better go. (GRUNTS)
He can come at any second.
And I don't want him coming and
finding roller skates on his feet.
Miss Patricia would find out
and she'd get angry.
etcetera.
(SNIFFLES)
(CASH REGISTER DINGS)
Thank you for coming in.
Yep. thanks.
JOSEPH: I can get you set up.
They're really easy to install.
This is an outdoor dome
infrared.
We can use as many as you want
in the apartment building.
You use a 16-channel HD DVR
in your security office.
One of the tenants got murdered
off-site and people are on edge.
They just wanna feel safe.
Totally get it.
DAVID: I'm gonna take a walk.
Yeah. I don't think that you
need to take a walk today. Dad.
Maybe tomorrow
or the next day.
No. I think I'm gonna
take a walk now.
(MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
You don't wanna take
a lot of walks.
You might get tired.
Let your dad
take a walk. Jesus.
Yeah.
Hey. do I know you?
Did you use to work
at the football stadium?
Fifteen years.
I used to hang out with some shady
types down at the stadium in my youth.
Turned it around
with positive thinking.
Should I ring this up?
We're gonna have to close early.
Yeah.
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(POLICE SIREN WAILING)
Peak transit time's over.
I missed them.
Come back tomorrow when
the factories are let out.
Can come back to the store and
we could do some inventory.
JOSEPH: (ON RADIO) Okay.
I'll see you back at the store.
(MUMBLING INCOHERENTLY)
You guys like cartoons?
So babyish.
I don't.
I like documentaries.
You watch documentaries?
I watched a documentary
about. um. space.
It's real big.
Sorry. bro.
(HEDWIG VOCALIZING)
DAVID: It's him. I saw a room.
It had red clay. Piles of it.
It's some kind of factory.
They're all in there.
JOSEPH: All right. Stand by.
I'll search the area.
(CHUCKLES) Boom! (GRUNTS)
Dad. I found a brick factory.
Uh. I's old. Abandoned.
Which direction?
To the south.
Dad?
(SCATTING)
MAN 1: You said
I could have those.
MAN 2: I know.
MAN 1: Taking everything
for yourself.
MAN 2: Take them.
Hey.
Oh. my God.
(GAGS)
MAN 1: You said
I could have those.
MAN 2: I know.
Take them.
(GRUNTS)
What?
MAN 1: Huh?
Taking everything
for yourself.
I don't know.
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
(GROANING)
(PANTING)
MAN 2: Who are you?
(AS THE BEAST)
I am you.
(METAL RATTLING)
(ALL BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GIRL SCREAMS)
(GIRLS SCREAMING)
(CHAINS RATTLING)
Come on!
(CRYING) Come on!
(GRUNTS)
(GIRLS WHIMPERING)
(THE BEAST GROWLING)
(GROWLING CONTINUES)
(LOUD THUDDING)
(GROWLING)
GIRL: Where did it go?
(THE BEAST PANTING. GROWLING)
(PANTING)
(ROARS)
(YELLS)
(GIRLS SCREAMING)
Leave! (GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(THE BEAST ROARING)
(GIRLS WHIMPERING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(DEBRIS CLATTERING)
(DAVID GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(STRAINING)
(THE BEAST YELLING)
(BOTH GROAN)
(GROWLS. PANTS)
(THE BEAST YELLING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
KEVIN: (AS BARRY) Don't.
Don't! Don't shoot!
(WHIMPERS)
We can work through this!
Just put the guns away!
(MUMBLES)
What's happening?
I didn't do anything!
My name is Barry! All right?
We have to get Kevin to stay in the light.
Just don't shoot us!
DR. STAPLE: Don't shoot!
He won't hurt anyone now.
You may find
a way out of here.
but you will have to hurt
a lot of officers.
A lot of people.
No one needs to get hurt
anymore. David.
OVERSEER:
It's gonna be okay. Joseph.
DR. STAPLE: (OVER SPEAKER) Take them
straight to Raven Hill Memorial.
The west wing
of Raven Hill Memorial.
(INDISTINCT CLAMORING
OVER RADIO)
(RADIO STOPS)
(GASPS)
(DOOR BUZZING)
OFFICER: No problem.
OFFICER: Keep moving.
Keep moving.
(AS HEINRICH)
Please. don't. Don't.
Don't. No.
OFFICER 2: Easy.
OFFICER 1: Hey! Hey!
(AS HEDWIG) We're cool. we're cool.
Totally cool.
All right? He doesn't like to be touched.
I can walk. I'll just walk.
Keep walking.
(DOOR CLOSES)
My name is Dr. Ellie Staple
and I'm a psychiatrist.
This room must look nefarious.
The walls are equipped
with 46 high-pressured nozzles
all connected to a 15.000-gallon
water tank outside.
It will only be triggered if you
are threatening or trying to escape.
This is a hypnosis light...
(AS DENNIS) Dennis.
My pleasure. Dennis.
Mmm-hmm.
You are being monitored.
If. for some reason. there's a
threatening identity in the room.
the light will
automatically strobe
and force a different identity
to take over.
DENNIS:
Who was the man?
He was as strong
as The Beast.
The man people in this city
have been talking about.
The only person to survive that
train wreck all those years ago.
I saw a video of you fighting
near a fire hydrant that erupted.
Saw you choke.
I think you believe
water is your weakness.
Where are you keeping him?
(THE BEAST EXHALES)
(ROARS)
(GROANS)
DR. STAPLE:
Everyone is safe. David.
Maybe this will all make sense
if I explain who I am.
I specialize in a particular
type of delusion of grandeur.
I specialize in those individuals
who believe they are superheroes.
I've been given three days to treat
you by whatever means necessary.
I came here for you both.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
ON PA)
PIERCE: Yo. this doctor comes in
here. takes over our wing.
tells us all new rules.
Rules of conduct.
How to treat people
with kindness.
(SCOFFS)
My whole life. all I do
is take care of people.
Come on. come on. come on.
There you go.
We got along just fine without
her. didn't we? Me and you?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(SLURPING)
Anyway...
(MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
You won't be lonely anymore.
You have two new friends.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Casey. could I see you
for a second?
I received a call
from your foster family.
Apparently.
it's on the news.
They caught the guy who abducted
you and murdered all those girls.
They caught the bastard.
Your foster family
is thrilled.
I can imagine how much relief
this causes you.
I'm sure you've been
thinking about him.
I have been thinking
about him.
They. uh. told me
to bring lots of options.
KEVIN: (AS JADE)
Hey. cutie.
Think you could help me?
I'm Jade.
They gave me a syringe for my
diabetes. but I dropped it.
My hands get shaky
when I get low blood sugar.
It's a little too close to the light.
Do you think you could pick it up for me?
(CHUCKLES)
Wow.
Stand up.
Let me get
a good look at you.
You are so tall.
Orwell and Barry are so angry
with me that I flipped.
But the truth is.
we really can do things
that you can't do.
I don't understand.
(GIGGLES)
(DARYL GRUNTS)
(KEVIN GROANING)
(AS IAN)
Hey. Hey. hey!
(GROANS)
I'm Ian.
All right? I'm Ian.
(AS MARY) And I'm Mary Reynolds.
We're twins.
Do you know
what would have happened
if she'd have gotten
to that key. you gobshite?
The Horde
would have killed ya.
(AS IAN) What've you got?
You get a little hard-on? Daryl.
Just calm down. okay?
(KEVIN GROANS)
(AS NORMA) I'm sorry for being with
the Horde. It's just... It's just...
Oh. do you know.
I am tired of being sorry.
You can call me Norma.
I am sorry about
the whole lying thing.
Though. I'm not lying.
Bro. just stop talking!
(AS JALIN)
I was so amped!
We almost got you. bro!
(LAUGHS)
Trying to keep him here
with this light thing?
That's some buttery shit.
DARYL: Stop talking.
(AS ANSEL) I'm not supposed
to be in the light.
Oh. we need more time.
Barry is speaking to Kevin.
Trying to get him nearer the light.
Is he close enough yet?
(AS B.T.) The only one
who can defend us is him.
Him!
(GROANING)
(AS PATRICIA) Where is the
man in the rain poncho?
Who is he?
Is he just a regular man?
I need to know.
All right. step away from the controls
now. little duck.
That's fine.
Now just walk away.
(DOOR LOCK BEEPS)
That's it. Just tip-toe away.
I try to come
once every week.
Sometimes. I admit.
I have neglected a week here and there.
He's changed over the years.
I can tell he's given up.
It's hard to see.
He thinks he was a mistake.
I'm not saying
he did good things.
He didn't.
Those poor people didn't
deserve to die like that.
But he's trying to make sense
of who he is.
Ain't we all doing that?
Yes. ma'am. we are.
They keep him
heavily sedated.
This is an enormous
amount of sedation.
He's too smart for 'em.
When they first
brought him here.
he memorized a blueprint
left out from an electrician
and short-circuited the power
to the whole hospital.
He's good
thinking through things.
He has this notion
that superheroes
are based on people like him.
and that other gentleman
I read is here.
Mr. Dunn.
Would it surprise you to know
there are more and more people
who have this delusion?
It is actually
the center of my work.
Yes. it would.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING
ON SPEAKERS)
MRS. PRICE: You don't let
them get you down. Elijah.
You hear me?
Stay proud.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Step back against the wall.
please.
(DOOR LOCK BEEPS)
(DOOR BUZZING)
(GENERATOR WHIRRING)
(WATER BUBBLING)
(COUGHING)
(DOOR BUZZES)
(DOOR OPENS)
(GRUNTS)
You're keeping him here
without guards?
I have to get out of here
before he gets out.
The individual who came
with you is contained.
David.
I would like you
to agree to have an MRI.
You were the sole survivor
of a devastating train
derailment 19 years ago.
It is possible
that there was damage to the frontal
lobe that you are unaware of.
(EXHALES)
Look at you. David.
You believe you have barely
enough strength to stand up.
You can't possibly explain
everything away.
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(AS MR. PRITCHARD)
Madam. I am Mr. Pritchard.
I'm a professor of cinema.
Specifically. Japanese.
1950s through the 1980s.
And I have absolutely no idea
what I'm doing here.
I am very much in favor
of Kevin's reemergence.
And yet. I find myself
in a goddamn prison cell.
And I can assure you
I am not...
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
Okay.
(YELPS)
(PANTING)
(AS FELIDA IN SPANISH)
(GRUNTS. GROWLS)
(AS HEDWIG IN ENGLISH)
I'm ready.
(WHIMPERS)
Young man. wait!
(SHOES SQUEAKING)
You will not be able
to get to the light.
It is set off by distance as well
as being monitored by a camera.
I know this seems very unfair to
you. (BLOWS RASPBERRY)
but you are stuck
in this room.
The guy The Beast fought.
he's right there!
He can't beat The Beast. He doesn't
think he can beat The Beast. does he?
Huh?
Beast like... (GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(WHISPERS) He doesn't think he
can beat The Beast. does he?
Beast like... (GRUNTS SOFTLY)
Your name is Hedwig. right?
You're nine. right?
HEDWIG: Yeah.
Forever?
(SIGHS)
No matter how many
experiences you have?
That must be so hard.
You treat people who think they're
comic book characters or something?
(EXHALES)
(CHUCKLES)
HEDWIG: I gotta go.
Miss Patricia says
she wants the light.
Hello. Patricia.
I'm Dr. Staple.
(AS PATRICIA) I've gathered.
As I understand it.
you're kind of the high priestess.
This cause isn't about me.
It's about The Beast. is it?
Where is he?
DR. STAPLE: Who?
The man.
He is guarded. isn't he?
He can't get out?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(JOSEPH CHATTERING
AND SNICKERING)
He's well-intentioned
and you would love him.
He's a huge...
He's a big trickster.
He's a great guy. He's got
a great sense of humor.
DR. STAPLE: So. let me recap
what you've told me.
Mmm-hmm.
Your dad is not the Green Guard
or "whatever his name is."
Your dad is a trickster.
and that I would love him.
He thought it would be fun
to be a do-gooder for a day.
Pretend he was this guy.
And with regard
to how he found the girls.
you retold a humorous story
where your dad thought the killer
might be in the factory area
because his friend Lou.
you referred to him as Louie
at a different point.
got mugged down there once.
Then your father
was walking by a building.
hears girls
screaming for help.
at which point you spiritedly
reenacted this moment in the story.
Thank you for that.
Then. your father
called you on the cell.
You told him
to call the police.
but he was.
"in it. you know. In it."
JOSEPH: Right.
I'll sign that
in front of a judge.
So. you see.
he shouldn't be here.
How long have you believed
your dad was a superhero?
There was a microphone
on his poncho.
I assume he was
communicating with you.
He talks to you when he's out on searches.
Doesn't he. Joseph?
He hasn't hurt anybody.
In the eyes of the authorities.
that is not accurate.
He's injured
countless individuals
who haven't had
their due process in court.
And there was a teenage girl
in this latest incident
who broke her arm and ribs.
No. They would all be murder
victims if it wasn't for my dad.
It was a vigilante event
and a victim was injured.
They will claim. in court.
that if they had found the girls.
no one would have been hurt.
Joseph.
I only have a few days.
If I don't get him
to give up his delusion.
he will remain in institutions
like this for the rest of his life.
No. he can't stay here.
Can I ask you
about your mother. Joseph?
What does that
have to do with this?
She passed away from acute
lymphoblastic leukemia five years ago.
That was cataclysmic
for you and your dad.
Yeah.
On the surface. Joseph.
you can see what I'm going to say. right?
You lost your mother.
You believe your father
is a real-life superhero.
You believe
he is almost immortal.
You can see how some would
say you need this to be true.
You just have to make sure you
are not more into this than he is.
YOUNG JOSEPH:
I'm not scared.
DAVID: That's great.
YOUNG JOSEPH: You know why?
I know now.
Know what?
Your secret identity.
That man was right.
Joseph.
There are big guys in almost
every gym that can lift that much.
You could've lifted more.
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone.
(ENGINE STARTING)
(DOOR OPENS)
DR. STAPLE: Just because he let you
go. doesn't mean he is good.
He's being held here
before his trial.
I'm in charge of him for now.
but everyone in this state
wants him tried and put away.
I'm trying to get the others
to stop thinking of this
as a superhuman being.
If they do. they will do the right
thing and keep him from the light.
Can I talk with them?
No.
Why?
Because it's not...
You're the victim.
(BEEPS)
(DOOR BUZZES)
(AS HEDWIG) No way!
You tried so hard to get away from
us and now you come back and see us?
You are so weird.
I like Drake now.
I liked Nicki for a while.
but then Nicki and Drake broke
up. and you can't like both.
This place is for people who think
that they're comic book characters.
And the Horde is kinda like a comic
book character name. isn't it?
Love comic books.
I'm sorry for trying to feed
you to The Beast. etcetera.
It's okay.
Can I talk to Dennis
or Patricia. please?
She was my girlfriend.
We kissed. (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(SOFTLY) Don't worry.
I haven't cheated on you.
(CHOKING)
(AS DENNIS)
What are you doin' here?
Your clothes are not dirty.
That's good.
Hello. Dennis.
A lot of people
have died.
Well...
You have to give up
the light.
They're never gonna
let you out of here.
The Horde has to give up
the light.
Listen to this doctor.
The doctor tells lies.
We will reveal that the
broken are the strongest.
The Beast will start
a revolution.
Is that what
Patricia told you to say?
The Beast is the highest form
of human evolution.
Dennis.
You guys are gonna die.
(GASPS) Casey.
(EXHALES)
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
(IN NORMAL TONE) Hey.
Kevin?
It's you.
You look different.
I wanted
to tell you something.
My uncle's in jail.
I put him there.
What he did to me was...
Wrong.
Just like what your mom
did to you was wrong.
We're the same?
I'm sorry.
I can't. I got...
Kevin. wait.
I've gotta go.
I've gotta go. (CHOKING)
(AS HEDWIG) The Horde is never
lettin' go of the light and...
(GASPS)
Do you like Kevin now?
Casey.
I need you.
The power of true. loving.
physical affection.
it's like something
supernatural.
It's the lack of it
that caused this
and only the true version
of it can heal it.
Will you help me?
DR. STAPLE: You are the last
person I need to see today.
You see this camera?
There are 100 more
of these.
Out of respect
for your cognitive abilities.
I have installed cameras
on every floor.
Every area. including every
direction of the exterior building.
We will see everything.
There is nowhere you can go
that won't be documented.
Elijah.
I've come to the conclusion that we
should perform a procedure on you.
This is a corrective procedure
that rebalances the part of the
frontal lobe that is overstimulated.
It would be an honor to get to
know your perspicacious mind.
We're going to conduct
the procedure in three days.
(CHEERING)
(MAN GRUNTING)
PLAYER: Right there.
right there!
(OLD-TIMEY MUSIC PLAYING
SOFTLY ON SPEAKERS)
Hey. my man.
How'd you get out
of your room?
You must have
left the door ajar.
He rolled out
toward the noise.
Wheel him back in
before the doctor sees.
Oh. you're too nice. Daryl.
You gotta be firm.
They'll walk all over you
otherwise.
He didn't touch any of the
medicines. did he?
No.
Right amounts.
(MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
DR. STAPLE: This will be
my final evaluation.
You gotta be kiddin' me.
This guy killed everyone on my train.
He's a mass murderer.
(CHAIN RATTLES)
DR. STAPLE: I understand that the
three of you think you are superhuman.
That you don't think
you are normal.
You've convinced yourselves
you have extraordinary gifts.
Like something
out of a comic book.
I am here to discuss the
possibility that you are mistaken.
Can you tell me
about Kevin's parents?
(SIGHS)
(AS DENNIS)
Kevin's mother
hurt Kevin.
And Kevin's father was gonna get
a doctor to try and stop her.
but he left.
I never wanted any of this.
What?
The killings.
Kevin Wendell Crumb.
(STRAINING)
(VOICES OVERLAP)
Kevin Wendell Crumb.
PENELOPE:
What did I tell you?
There is no running in the
house. Kevin Wendell Crumb!
DR. STAPLE: Kevin?
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Kevin.
(IN NORMAL TONE) Why do you
all keep bringing me back?
I don't wanna be here.
The need for the particular
story we tell ourselves
begins somewhere. Kevin.
From a memory.
What?
I don't...
Hey. where's that girl?
Casey? She...
(CHOKES)
(AS HEDWIG) Everybody wants
the light now.
They're all fighting.
etcetera.
And Miss Patricia's yelling at me.
sayin' I gotta hold on to the light.
She said I have one job to do.
keep Kevin out of the light.
So. I'm sorry.
you won't see him anymore.
(SPUTTERS AND EXHALES SHARPLY)
And you have to
listen to her. right?
Because she's an adult
and you're not.
Duh. Yeah.
Was he cryin'?
Jeez. pussy.
Listen. I don't know
about these other guys.
but we are like a superhero.
No? We're like...
(IMITATES FANFARE)
We're not crazy!
David...
I don't think this applies
just to Kevin
and his disorder.
(SIGHS)
Is there a memory?
What you're looking for
is a moment of weakness
that made you possibly entertain
the idea of being super strong.
There is a reason I ask you.
This is your MRI. David.
This is your frontal lobe.
There is a questionable cloud
right here.
There is the possibility that that
is damage from that train accident.
I'm supposed to believe
this means something?
It's just this.
plus an anchoring incident
and you would have the pattern
for this disorder that I treat.
I hate to see you like this.
This is not
how I would've done things.
I don't approve
of how they've handled you.
Elijah. because of
your condition.
I didn't have to do
an MRI on you.
There are a few in your file.
You definitely have one of the
markers for this disorder. Elijah.
As do you. Kevin.
These are the medical reasons I'm
thinking you have this disorder.
Now let's deal with
why you think you don't.
How do you know who's
good and who's bad. David?
Convince me.
It's a feeling.
An intuition?
When you see someone?
I have to touch them.
What does the intuition
feel like?
A vision.
A moment.
A sin.
You kinda have to
interpret it.
Have you ever seen very
good magicians. David?
I mean. the very best.
They are trained
as mentalists.
and they can do
seemingly extraordinary feats.
They accomplish these feats by
interpreting hundreds of cues
that an individual is giving
off in a split second.
I think you are like these
professional guessers. David.
You are world-class at it.
Simply extraordinary at it.
But it is based
on real things
and you are making
the picture.
It is not coming to you
through mystical means.
These are the clothes
that the patient next to you
came in
with when he arrived.
There's red clay
staining the pants.
It's very visible.
Is it possible that you saw
something on the news...
Sorry. bro. ...Then saw an
adult acting like a child?
Someone who fit the bill
of someone with this disorder.
Intuited. "This might be
the person I'm looking for."
Saw the red clay.
and thought he might be hiding
in a place with red clay?
No.
You're certain?
You're creating a chain of
thoughts that never happened.
(LAUGHING)
(AS PATRICIA) You really
dissected him. Doctor.
Good for you.
DR. STAPLE: As I understand
it. there were many videos
of world-class rock climbers
on the computer in your office
at the zoo.
It was kind of an obsession.
Some of those climbers could actually
scale a literal wall. couldn't they?
(EXHALES)
What's your point. Doctor?
It was
a practical observation
that produced a practical
skill set in an alter.
Mmm.
Then how did he bend
the bars?
The iron bars at the zoo?
You did see those.
didn't you?
That's not in our heads.
The cages beneath the zoo were made
in 1874 when the zoo first opened.
I was able to bend them
by putting a wrench
between them and leaning back.
Difficult. again.
But possible.
No!
What about the shotgun?
He was shot.
Not once but twice.
What does your sleeping mind
think of that?
We've analyzed the shotgun
and the cartridges.
They were very old.
There was a lot of moisture
from the boiler room
down in the locker area
where they were kept.
The cartridges were
possibly compromised.
And some of the pellets
hit the inside of the bars.
(CHUCKLES)
It is at least possible
that there is a practical
explanation for this.
Mmm-mmm.
What if I suggested
something upsetting. Patricia?
Like The Beast isn't
as powerful as you think.
He's not much more powerful
than a strong man.
The facts you are basing
your belief in are wrong.
If superheroes exist.
why are there only three of you?
CASEY: When was
the first comic book written?
The first reprints of newspaper
strips in tabloid size
happened in 1929.
And then. in 1938.
the apotheosis happened.
Action Comics Number One
launched
with the man in the cape and
the blue tights on the cover.
Boo-yah!
(LAUGHS) Here we are.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING
ON SPEAKERS)
Thank you.
What are you doing
back there?
You're not one of those
Hello Kitty pervs?
JOSEPH: I'm just looking
for something.
Prove to someone
I'm not crazy.
I'm leaving.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
Oh. my God!
(GASPS)
GIRL: Catch!
BOY 1: You're it!
I'm it. You're it!
BOY 2: Oh. no!
(CASEY CHUCKLES)
You're it!
Let's play hot potato. guys!
GIRL: Let's play hot potato!
KIDS: (SINGING) Hot
potato Hot potato
Hot potato
Hot potato. hot potato.
hot potato Hot potato. hot potato. hot
BOY 1: You're out.
GIRL: You're out.
BOY 2: Come on. ready?
BOY 1: No!
GIRL: No!
KIDS: (SINGING) Hot
potato Hot potato
Hot potato
Hot potato. hot potato. hot
I'm just asking you to bring
in a package if you see one
instead of stepping over it
to come in the house.
(DOOR SLAMS)
Hello?
(DOOR LOCK BEEPS)
(DOOR BUZZES)
If. by mistake. I drop
this heavy flashlight
on your paper legs
no one would come check on you
for some time.
Not until Daryl gets here
for his shift.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
Have you been getting
out of your room. Elijah?
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
I must be losing my mind.
(ENGINE BACKFIRES)
(WHEELCHAIR CREAKS)
PIERCE: Night. Joe.
JOE: Have a good night.
PIERCE: Daryl.
Hey. my man.
You almost made it.
(CHUCKLES) I think
your watch is fast.
Joe. my man!
How's it going?
What's going on?
What's happening?
Looking tired. man.
You still taking that multi-vitamin?
Not like I should.
Yeah. but listen.
you gotta take the D.
If you don't take
Vitamin D.
none of that stuff's going
to absorb into your body.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
(WHISPERS)
Clarence Wendell Crumb.
(GASPS)
(CHUCKLES)
Take a little bit of
grape seed extract
and it'll keep it all
in there.
You'll absorb it
into your body faster.
Let me ask you.
how much water you drinking?
Not enough.
Yeah. I know.
(DOOR LOCK BEEPS)
(DOOR BUZZES)
(WHEELS SQUEAKING)
(AS PATRICIA) How?
How did you get here
without anyone seeing?
The sound of
a car backfiring occurs
when unburned fuel vapor is
ignited by a very hot muffler
upon the car
being turned off.
Daryl. who takes over
at 11:00 p.m..
suffers from this particular
vehicular malady.
It happened
seven minutes ago.
Couple that with the fact
that I've overheard complaints
about how long it takes him
to get to his desk.
He's a bit of a talker.
you see.
I estimate I have
two to three minutes left.
Someone has been pretending.
Pilfered the aspirin bottle.
Replaced the original dose of medicine
with the same amount of aspirin.
Did sleight of hand with the
pills given to me to take daily.
What do you want?
Ma'am.
I'm here to see if the tales of
the extraordinary being are real.
The half-man. half-creature.
Patricia.
But I appreciate
your manners.
I don't know anymore.
I'm a comic book expert.
Patricia.
I believe comic books are a
continuation of documentation
that has gone on for centuries
of what humans are capable of.
That they are what someone.
somewhere. saw or felt.
Are you aware that spandex.
the underwear on the outside. and boots
come from strongmen
in the circus in the 1930s?
No.
The freak show men who could do
incredible feats of strength.
I urge you to look past the
capes and monologuing villains.
Are you with me?
Yes.
I only have a minute left.
I believe The Beast
may be part of this.
There are references
to man/animal characters.
The dual character.
The man who has abilities like animals.
I'd like to meet The Beast.
see if he's real.
If he is. then I'll get us all
out of here tomorrow night.
(SNIFFLING)
What's upsetting you.
Patricia?
What if he can't do
these extraordinary things?
What if he is just unwell?
Like you.
Everything extraordinary
can be explained away
and yet it is true.
I think deep down
you know this.
Everything we will see and do
will have a basis in science.
But it will have limits.
This is the real world.
not a cartoon.
And yet. some of us
don't die from bullets.
Some of us
can still bend steel.
That is not a fantasy.
Hmm.
If you really think
you can get us all out.
then you may meet The Beast.
But for your sake.
I hope he likes you.
Tomorrow night.
Call a board meeting
or whatever.
What do we call you. sir?
First name. Mister.
Last name. Glass.
(DOOR LOCK BEEPS)
(DOOR OPENS)
(MOANS) What's going on?
Be careful. Not too much
pressure when restraining him.
Dr. Staple.
what are you doing?
It's a sedative.
What?
I'm sorry to do this. Elijah.
Ow!
We saw footage of you
leaving your room last night.
It seems you have been duping us.
No! No.
I've moved up the procedure
to this morning.
Wait. I have...
DR. STAPLE: Thank you
for being careful. everyone.
Good luck. Elijah.
DR. STAPLE: Nothing essential is
going to change about who you are.
I promise. my friend.
(SWITCH CLICKS)
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
(CHATTER AND LAUGHTER)
(MAN SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY
ON PA)
Whoo!
(LAUGHS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Elijah!
Whoo!
MAN: (ON PA)
So. let's all scream!
(RIDERS WHOOPING
AND SCREAMING)
(SOBS) Elijah!
CONDUCTOR: Ma'am.
get a hold of yourself.
Mama!
(GRUNTING)
(BONES BREAKING)
(SCREAMS)
MRS. PRICE: Elijah!
Stop the ride!
Ma'am. step down.
MRS. PRICE: Stop the ride!
(PANTING)
(KEYS JANGLING)
(CAR LOCK CHIRPS)
(BEEPS)
(DOOR BUZZES)
(OLD-TIMEY MUSIC PLAYING
ON SPEAKERS)
Dinner. Elijah.
How you doing?
You'll feel better tomorrow.
Pictures are crooked.
Hey.
(GRUNTS)
Took a bitch-ass long time
to find the right piece.
(CHOKING)
First name. Mister.
Last name. Glass.
(BEEPING)
(DARYL CONTINUES CHOKING)
You don't know
what it's like. Daryl.
To be so different.
you don't know where you fit.
It's an awful feeling.
(BEEPS)
KEVIN: (AS LUKE)
Hey there. buddy. What's up?
Patricia told us
you were coming.
My name is Luke.
and I am Team Horde all the way.
Yeah. I can intro you to everybody.
I ain't no bad hombre to know.
Everybody's gonna tell you
that I got a big mouth. though.
I spoil the end of movies.
Ain't true.
Everybody knows the priest dies
at the end of The Exorcist.
(KEVIN GRUNTS)
(AS GODDARD) The American Sublime.
Do you even know what that means?
No.
That is why this world
is a lost cause.
That is why The Beast is the only
thing that is pure and meaningful...
ELIJAH: American Sublime
refers to Western paintings
of landscapes and seascapes
depicting the immensity of nature.
The use of violent storms in the
distance was a common practice.
Painting's of particular
interest to me.
(GRUNTS)
(KEVIN GROANS)
(AS HEDWIG) Hey. Miss Patricia
says that your bones can break
if I. like.
(CLICKS TONGUE) tap them.
Is that true?
Yes.
(EXHALES)
Uh. so. what's your superpower?
Your mind?
(WHOOSHES)
What's mine?
You're nine forever.
right?
Yeah.
That's incredible.
You can see the world the
way it really is. Always.
Kid who can never grow old.
(CHUCKLES)
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Whoa!
This place is so cool.
Mr. Glass.
I feel like dancing.
Then go ahead and dance.
Yeah! Check it!
(HUMMING)
Yeah.
Oh. man.
(KEVIN GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(THE BEAST GROWLING)
ELIJAH:
They've been lying to us all.
(AS THE BEAST)
You believe?
Yes. I do.
It's what I've believed
my whole life.
They are losing faith.
My Horde is losing faith!
In comics.
you would go to a public
place. where all could see you.
A place celebrating man's
pedestrian achievements.
But you need David
to convince them.
You should fight him
in front of the world.
The tallest building in
this city is opening today.
All the cameras in the
world will record you.
You can convince the Horde
and the world
at the same time.
we exist.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Why are you in this chair.
child?
My bones break easily.
I was born this way.
I've had 94 breaks
in my life.
I've known only pain.
Rejoice.
You have suffered
and are now pure.
I assume you were sent here
to be an avenging angel.
How much do you want
to avenge us?
(YELLING)
Well. that sounds like
the bad guys teaming up.
ELIJAH: (ON SPEAKERS)
How you doing. David?
I always thought of us
as friends.
Elijah?
ELIJAH: You shouldn't be
hiding in the shadows. David.
You're able to hide
because people who steal cars
and mug people in alleys
don't need
your full potential.
You're only using
one percent of your abilities
with these petty criminals.
Maybe there's nothing
to hide. Elijah.
I have found someone who will require
your full potential to come out.
A superhuman serial killer.
Don't do this.
(SIGHS)
How can we be
the only ones?
Maybe we believed something
that isn't even true.
(SIGHS)
We are going to the tallest
building in the city.
The Horde is going to be
revealed there.
There are three floors
that house a chemical company
in that building.
I am going to blow up that building
using their chemicals. David.
You might want to
try and stop us.
Today is
your coming-out party.
At least you know
what to wear.
(BEEPING)
(AIR HISSING)
(BUTTON CLICKS)
I've turned off the water
hoses in your room. David.
There's only the door left.
Elijah.
It's metal.
But you can't get through it.
because people's bones
break against metal.
and you're nothing special.
A lot of people
are going to die. Overseer.
if you don't get through
that door.
(SWITCH CLICKS)
(SIGHS)
Hi.
(DOOR BUZZES)
(FLIES BUZZING)
I'm here.
(BUTTON CLICKS)
(SWITCH CLICKS)
Daryl?
(WHEELS SQUEAKING IN DISTANCE)
(SQUEAKING CONTINUES)
This is where
they would paint you
with big eyes and bubbles of
confusion above your head.
(SOFT THUD)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(AS THE BEAST)
You hurt him?
What are you doing?
You should kneel before him.
He is the broken.
PIERCE: Step away from me.
(GRUNTING)
Get back in your room!
Both of you!
(GRUNTS)
(BONES CRUNCHING)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMING)
(THE BEAST GRUNTING)
(PIERCE GASPING)
(SNARLING)
You're fighting
for the broken.
You found your purpose.
(THE BEAST GRUNTING)
(PIERCE GASPING)
(BONES CRUNCH)
(GASPS)
(PIERCE GRUNTS)
(THE BEAST BREATHING HEAVILY)
(THE BEAST GRUNTING)
(BONES CRUNCH)
(THE BEAST GRUNTS)
(BODY THUDS)
(SIGHS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTING)
One of the Horde may need to walk
us out of here. if that's okay...
Partner.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
(YELLS)
(YELLS AND GRUNTS)
(BEEPS)
(DOOR BUZZES)
ELIJAH: Go through
the basement.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(GRUNTS)
DR. STAPLE:
Listen to me. Joseph.
Your father is making
great progress.
I'm very hopeful for him.
Did you know
the first Superman
couldn't even fly?
And Metropolis is actually
New York City.
And what about all the
coincidences in what I was reading?
DR. STAPLE: Comic books
are an obsession.
Have you ever been
to a comic book convention?
They sell
teen TV shows there.
They are selling things.
Your friends and family members
have lost their perspective.
Your dad is trying
to fight her abductor.
Your son is trying
to best his dad.
He's the anarchist. he's the
brains. he's the reluctant hero.
This all sounds
very familiar. doesn't it?
Comic books
are not valid history.
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
GUARD: Hey.
what wing are you with?
(AS PATRICIA) Uh. The Beast
is saying that he'd like you
to roll forward
when they come.
I believe.
(STRAINS)
(GROANS)
(THE BEAST BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(BEEPS)
(DOOR BUZZES)
(INAUDIBLE)
(REMOTE CLICKS)
The new Osaka building opens
today with much fanfare.
Thousands are expected to
come out for the ceremony.
Many just want to see
the spectacular architecture.
Now. this building is expected to
be the hub of the business community
creating thousands of jobs...
We have a Code Three.
All patients
locked in their rooms.
Grounds security on alert.
(ON SPEAKERS) The patients
are planning to go
to the public opening of the Osaka
Tower. the tallest building.
Elijah may be intending to
compromise a chemical facility there.
Please alert the Philadelphia
Police Department.
They made a mistake
going through the basement.
It gives us some time.
MRS. PRICE: I remember something
about a classic public forum
where the climax of
limited editions end.
I think he said it was
referred to as the "showdown."
where all the skills are revealed
and pitted against each other.
And then?
What happens?
(THUDS)
(GASPS)
(THE BEAST YELLING)
Christ! They're out here!
They're out here!
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
(ALARM BLARING)
This is Dr. Ellie Staple.
We will need assistance at
Raven Hill Memorial immediately.
(ALARM CONTINUES BLARING)
(BOTH SCREAMING AND GRUNTING)
WOMAN: No!
(WOMEN SCREAM)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
(AS DENNIS) How many people
are gonna die today?
Huh?
I don't wanna do this.
I don't care what Patricia says.
I'm not... (STRAINING)
Hedwig's taking the light.
(AS HEDWIG) Hey. what's up?
(STRAINING)
(AS PATRICIA) Don't worry.
(PANTING)
We don't need him anyway.
There are still 10 of us.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
It appears The Beast
is not done here yet.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
(THE BEAST YELLING)
We've got eyes on him.
Please advise.
(THE BEAST BREATHING HEAVILY)
Please advise!
(GRUNTING)
(ROARS)
(GUARDS GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(DOOR OPENS)
The collection
of main characters.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GROWLS)
(ROARING)
(ALARM CONTINUES BLARING)
(THE BEAST ROARING)
(ROARING)
Keep patients and staff away
from the south-side windows.
Authorities are on their way.
(GRUNTING LOUDLY)
(WOMEN WHIMPERING)
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
Okay. I got you. (GRUNTING)
(BOTH WHIMPERING)
You will learn to kneel
before the broken.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
(CHOKING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(CONTINUES CHOKING)
(GRUNTING)
(OFFICERS SHOUTING
INDISTINCTLY)
CASEY: I need to explain.
He has DID.
He believes he's an animal.
OFFICER: Keep moving.
No. you don't understand.
All he knows is pain.
You're going to get hurt.
Somebody. please...
He has DID.
We can get the compassionate
people inside him to help you.
Stay here. ELIJAH: You're
the girl The Beast let go.
(YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
(SHOUTS)
(OFFICERS GRUNTING)
OVERSEER:
Stay away from him.
(SHOUTS)
Go!
(ALL GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
(OFFICERS SCREAM)
OVERSEER: I'm just trying
to save you.
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
(GROWLING)
(WHIMPERING)
(METAL CREAKING)
(FLESH SQUELCHING)
(GRUNTS)
DR. STAPLE: Casey. the light
won't work out here now.
You have to be the one
to get Kevin to come out.
We need to get them inside
to safety. Do you hear me?
JOSEPH: (ON SPEAKERS) Dad.
there are two tactical teams on the way.
OVERSEER: Get back inside!
(BOTH WHIMPERING)
Hurry. Get inside
the building.
(BOTH PANTING)
(THE BEAST PANTING)
ELIJAH: The water
used for David's room.
There's water in that tank.
I know he almost drowned
when he was a child.
Water is his weakness.
JOSEPH: Hey!
Hey!
OVERSEER: Joseph!
JOSEPH:
He's lying to you.
In comics.
the parents of the villains always
hold a key to understanding them.
He's not
telling you something.
OVERSEER: Joseph. get back.
(THE BEAST BREATHING HEAVILY)
Don't tell him yet.
Kevin's dad didn't just take
any train and not come home.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
TRAIN ANNOUNCER: Eastrail 177.
Next stop. Philadelphia.
JOSEPH: He took the train
my dad was on.
The one that everyone died
except my dad.
That's the key
to who you are.
Mr. Glass killed Kevin's dad.
(PANTING)
(GROWLING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
ELIJAH: It's all evidence.
you see?
If that train crash
hadn't happened.
Kevin wouldn't have been
left alone with his mother.
If Kevin's mother wasn't allowed
to continue to abuse him.
then The Beast
wouldn't have had to be born.
What are the odds
that David Dunn
and Clarence Wendell Crumb
would be together that day?
Amazing.
I created you
as I created David.
It just took longer.
Nineteen years.
They almost convinced me
I was crazy.
I create superheroes.
I truly am a mastermind.
I thank you for what you did.
But I came to protect Kevin.
And I cannot trust you
to keep him safe.
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS)
OVERSEER: Hey.
We still haven't settled
that kneeling thing.
(LAUGHING) The classic turn.
The enemy becomes the ally
because of the hero's
unflinching sense of good.
(GRUNTS)
(ELIJAH GROANS)
(COUGHS. GROANS)
(THE BEAST GRUNTING)
(BONES CRACK)
(SCREAMING)
(COUGHING)
(CONTINUES COUGHING)
We will finish this
in front of the world.
(SIRENS WAILING)
(MRS. PRICE PANTING)
(ELIJAH GROANING)
Elijah.
(GASPING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Release me.
(STRAINING)
Let me talk to
Kevin Wendell Crumb.
(STRAINING)
No!
(THE BEAST GRUNTING)
Release me.
I need to talk to
Kevin Wendell Crumb.
(CHOKING)
He needs me.
Kevin Wendell Crumb.
(YELLS)
(KEVIN PANTING)
(IN NORMAL TONE) Hey.
The Beast listened to me.
He couldn't do what he wanted.
You can tell him what to do.
I'm not in charge
of the light.
Yes!
Yes. you are.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
It feels good.
Doesn't it?
Mmm-hmm.
Will you stay in the light
with me?
For a little while?
(SILENCED GUNSHOT)
(CHOKING)
(GRUNTS)
OFFICER: She was able
to turn him. Target down.
You guys gotta help him.
That's my dad.
He's trying to help you guys.
The guy in the green.
that's my dad.
He's trying to stop the Horde.
He's really weak.
(COUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING CONTINUES)
David.
David. take my hand.
Take it now!
(STRAINING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CHATTER STOPS)
It's just us.
DR. STAPLE: They sent me here
for you three.
Tell me the truth.
Did I almost convince you
you were an ordinary man?
I would have left you alone.
but when the Horde
showed up here.
then I just had to come.
MRS. PRICE: Didn't you tell me
there was a showdown
at the end of
a limited edition?
How come you didn't know
how it was gonna end?
No. Mama.
This is not a limited edition.
This was an origin story
(COUGHS) the whole time.
(GROANS)
What's happening?
(GRUNTS)
(CRYING)
(AS HEDWIG) I like being nine.
(SNIFFLING)
It hurts. Casey.
Get it to stop hurting.
(CHOKING)
I can't hold on
to the light. Casey.
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
(CRYING)
(AS DENNIS) I should never
have listened to her.
(PAINED GRUNTING)
Now these pants got blood
on them. They're ruined.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
We gotta clean these pants.
Casey.
(CHOKING)
(AS SAMUEL)
As his body slowly succumbs
to the inevitable.
a sensation of cold water
spreads through his body.
His thoughts are
a mixture of fear
and sweet relief.
(STRAINING)
(AS POLLY)
Ladies and gentlemen.
here's Patricia.
We should all listen to her.
(STRAINS)
(AS PATRICIA)
Did you see them?
They are both extraordinary.
I never doubted...
Never let them tell you
I doubted it.
(GASPING)
(IN NORMAL TONE)
They're all so scared.
But I told them that I'm gonna
hold the light now.
You really my friend?
Then I'm gonna
hold the light till the end.
Till the very end.
It's not so bad
being in the light.
(GASPING)
(SOFTLY) Kevin.
(INAUDIBLE)
DR. STAPLE: Would you mind stepping
away for a moment so I can check him?
It's okay.
(ELIJAH COUGHS)
(ELIJAH GASPS)
They got it wrong
in the comics.
They talk about secret evil
groups trying to stop the heroes.
I don't think we are
particularly evil
and we don't choose sides.
We try to stop both of you.
If there is one of you.
the opposite of you appears.
It escalates. We step in.
There just can't be gods
amongst us.
It's not fair.
It has worked just fine
for 10.000 years our way.
Take consolation in the fact that
you were right about your theory.
Be at peace.
I wasn't a mistake. Mama.
MRS. PRICE: No.
You were spectacular.
Oh.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
DR. STAPLE: These patients
were very disturbed.
Let me just simply state.
everything that occurred was
related to drugs in their systems
or their heightened
state of mania.
For the patients' privacy.
let's keep what happened in this building
and this parking lot to ourselves.
REPORTER:
...general public alike.
Opening ceremonies
have concluded.
but from the looks on the
faces of the thousands...
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CHATTER STOPS)
DR. STAPLE:
All three were real.
Quite special. actually.
If you approve.
I will move to the next city.
WOMAN: Will there be
any repercussions?
DR. STAPLE:
No one saw them.
I know what my charge is.
Convince them.
This is the most humane
and effective method.
We're not executioners.
and we don't need martyrs.
If that fails.
use the machine.
And I understand how important
what we're doing is.
Maintaining balance.
keeping order.
BATMAN: (ON TV) We're not here
to buy umbrellas and you know it.
ROBIN: Spread your wings.
Mr. K. G. Bird.
We're flying you down
to headquarters.
THE PENGUIN:
On what charge. Boy Wonder?
ROBIN: Illegal umbrellas.
BATMAN: Assault and battery.
disturbing the peace.
We've got enough to put
you back on ice. Penguin.
(UPBEAT ROCK SONG PLAYING
ON SPEAKERS)
He's too smart.
That's why
he's the mastermind.
He'll never tell you
his real plan.
He sets everybody up.
Gets them looking in one direction.
BOY: So cool. man.
There's always
a real plan.
You see this camera?
There are 100 more
of these.
Everything is being recorded.
All videos and all back-up
videos have been erased. correct?
GUARD: Yes.
Was any of it downloaded
before that?
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
GUARD: I don't know
how this is possible.
Someone was streaming the live
security feed to a private site.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
He went through the
basement tunnels to be seen
by as many cameras
as possible.
That's why he didn't go out
the side entrance.
He was never planning
on going to that building.
This was a suicide mission.
I gave him all the cameras
he needed right here.
What have you done. Elijah?
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SCREAMING)
(SIGHS)
(KIDS PLAYING OUTSIDE)
(COMPUTER CHIMES)
(SIGHS)
(MOUSE CLICKS)
ELIJAH: (ON SPEAKERS)
There are unknown forces
that don't want us to realize
what we are truly capable of.
They don't want us to know
the things we suspect are
extraordinary about ourselves are real.
(COMPUTER CHIMES)
I believe
that if everyone sees
what just a few people become when
they wholly embrace their gifts.
others will awaken.
Belief in oneself
is contagious.
We give each other permission
to be superheroes.
We will never
awaken otherwise.
(KIDS CHATTERING)
Whoever these people are
who don't want us
to know the truth.
today they lose.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Thanks.
How long's it been
since we posted it?
Two hours.
How long
will it be before...
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
ON PA)
(INAUDIBLE CONVERSATIONS)
(SIGHS. SNIFFLES)
(EXHALES)
I know what this is.
This is the moment we are
let in on the universe.
(INAUDIBLE)
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today